Guide to the Washington Office on Latin America Records, 1962-2020 and undated, bulk 1974-2005; 1962-ongoing RL.01401
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Accession (2013-0053), 39 boxes
  - Miscellaneous Files
    - Southcom Posture Statement, 2003 (Box 476)
    - Southcom Posture Statement, 2004 (Box 476)
    - Southcom Posture Statement, 2005 (Box 476)
    - Southcom Enduring Friendship, 2005 (Box 476)
    - Merida Initiative Fact Sheets, 2008 (Box 476)
    - Report on Training of Special Operations Forces, 1998 (Box 476)
    - Company B. Special Operations Counterdrug Training, 1998 (Box 476)
    - Drawdown to Provide Counterdrug Assistance to Colombia, Peru, Ecuador, and Panama, 1999 (Box 476)
    - US/Mexico DoD Counterdrug, 1998 (Box 476)
    - Department of Defense, Special Operations, Low Intensity Conflict, 1998 (Box 476)
    - Humanitarian and Civic Assistance, 1998 (Box 476)
    - Report on Department of Defense Expenditures to Support Foreign Counterdrug Activities, 2000 (Box 476)
    - Counterdrug Support, Latin America/Caribbean Program, 1999 (Box 476)
    - Mexico Report to Compass, 1999 (Box 476)
    - Colombian Helicopter Transfer, 1998 (Box 476)
    - Merida Initiative, 2007 (Box 477)
    - Merida Breakdown, 2008 (Box 477)
    - Mexico-Corchado-Drugs, 2007 (Box 477)
    - Paraguay - Decidamos, Comporna po la Expresion Cindadana, 2008 (Box 477)
    - Brazil-Paraguay Bimodal Transportation project, Darana, 2007 (Box 477)
    - Paraguay-Cultura Politica y Sobernabilidad Democratica, 2006 (Box 477)
    - Paraguay Trade, 2007 (Box 477)
    - Paraguay, 2007 (Box 477)
    - Transparencia Paraguay, 2008 (Box 477)
    - Guatemala-Violence Against Women, 2006 (Box 477)
    - Bolivia Agrarian Reform, 2006 (Box 477)
    - Bolivia WG/Information, 2007 (Box 477)
    - Paraguay, 2005 (Box 477)
    - Board Staff Meeting/ARCA Proposal, 2002 (Box 478)
    - Other: Cuba, Misc. print materials, 2002 (Box 478)
    - Pugrrash-Cuban Medical Advances, 2001 (Box 478)
    - Cuba News Newsletter, 2002-2003 (Box 478)
    - Cuba General Information, 2004 (Box 478)
    - Cuba Legislation/Hill work, 2007 (Box 478)
    - Nebraska, Cuba, 2002 (Box 478)
    - Kansas, 2002 (Box 478)
    - Background on Kansas Contacts, 2002 (Box 478)
    - "Demystifying Cuba, circa 1997 (Box 478)
    - "List the US Embargo on Food and Medicine to Cuba" LAWCO, 1998 (Box 478)
    - Cuba- Religion Licensing OFAC, 2005-2006 (Box 478)
    - American Human Trade with Cuba, 1998 (Box 478)
    - Americans for Humanitarian Trade with Cuba, 1998 (Box 478)
    - Cuba Workplan Update, 2001 (Box 478)
    - Cuba: WOLA mailings, 2003 (Box 478)
    - Presentacion a Personal de WOLA El Salvador- Citizen Security, circa 2006 (Box 479)
    - Youth Camps- El Salvador, 2006-2007 (Box 479)
    - Police Report Cover Letter- El Salvador, 1996 (Box 479)
    - Hamilton Letter- El Salvador, 1995 (Box 479)
    - G. V. Article- Harvard Review- El Salvador, 1995 (Box 479)
    - El Salvador LAWG, 1995 (Box 479)
    - El Salvador Police Update, 1998 (Box 479)
    - El Salvador Press Release, 1998 (Box 479)
    - El Salvador Police Memo/News Articles, 1995 (Box 479)
    - El Salvador Drop and Article, 1995 (Box 479)
    - San Francisco Chronicle- El Salvador, 1998 (Box 479)
    - Delegation Report- El Salvador, 1995 (Box 479)
    - El Salvador- Press Release re: Arrest of Alfarco, 1995 (Box 479)
    - El Salvador- Watson Memo, 1998 (Box 479)
    - Dear Colleague Drop, 1995 (Box 479)
    - El Salvador Trip-McGovern, 2005-2006 (Box 479)
    - El Salvador- DC/Memo, 2006 (Box 479)
    - El Salvador- Calls, 2006 (Box 479)
    - El Salvador: Transnational Youth Gangs, 2007 (Box 479)
    - El Salvador: "Land and Peace in Post-War El Salvador" Foley, circa 1997 (Box 479)
    - Gangs Legislation, 2008 (Box 479)
    - El Salvador Elections, The Voter Registration Tangle, 1993-1994 (Box 479)
    - El Salvador Development Group, 2001 (Box 479)
    - Pilot Project Kansas, Nebraska, 2002 (Box 480)
    - Kansas Communication, 2002 (Box 480)
    - Funder Correspondence- Cuba Project, 2001 (Box 480)
    - Proposal and Reports Arca Foundation, Cuba, 2001 (Box 480)
    - Myths and Facts and Other, Cuba, 1997 (Box 480)
    - Cuba, Embargo, 2000 (Box 480)
    - State Legislation Resolutions on Cuba: Texas, Illinois, Louisiana, 2006 (Box 480)
    - Cuba: "Engagement or Isolation" WOLA, 1997 (Box 480)
    - Cuba: "Crossing the Divide", WOLA, 1997 (Box 480)
    - Cuba: Report on Torture…at Guantanamo Bay, 2006 (Box 480)
    - Labor Delegation: Cuba, 2003 (Box 480)
    - Joel-Nicaragua Faxes, 2006 (Box 481)
    - HR 1081, Domestic Violence, 2006 (Box 481)
    - Schakowsky Andean Free Trade Deal, 2005 (Box 481)
    - Mexico Strike Letter, 2006 (Box 481)
    - Brazil Delegation, 2005 (Box 481)
    - Vicki Gass, Correspondence, 2001-2008 (Box 481)
    - Misc. Correspondence, 2007-2008 (Box 481)
    - Gangs- Religious Service Prov. Ecumenical Advocacy Days, 2006 (Box 481)
    - Guatemala- "Juventud, Seguridad, y Justicia con CentroAmerica", 2008 (Box 481)
    - Guatemala, 2005 (Box 481)
    - Orlando and Claudia, 2006 (Box 481)
    - Giovana Lemus, 2006 (Box 481)
    - PLANOVI, 2004 (Box 481)
    - FAFG Letter, 2005 (Box 481)
    - Rios Mott et. Al. - Spanish case, 2006 (Box 481)
    - Faxes- Fem- Senate, 2006 (Box 481)
    - Coyuntura Documents, 2006 (Box 481)
    - CHRC Dear Colleague, undated (Box 481)
    - El Salvador lists- religious, undated (Box 481)
    - ICJ, 2005 (Box 481)
    - Dear Colleague Thank You Notes, 2006 (Box 481)
    - Press Release List- DC letter SEDEM list, 2006 (Box 481)
    - AB Trip, 2006 (Box 481)
    - DECOPAZ, Guatemala, 1997 (Box 481)
    - Guatemala- Robbery at La Aurora Airport, 2006 (Box 481)
    - Programa Espana- PNUD para el fortalecimiento de la sobertanbilidad con Controamerica, 1996 (Box 481)
    - UNC Evidentiary Considerations in Gender-Based Violence: Recommendations for Mexico and Guatemala, 2007 (Box 481)
    - CICIG, 2007 (Box 481)
    - Millennium Challenge Corporation, 2006; 1 of 2 (Box 482)
    - Millennium Challenge Corporation, 2006; 2 of 2 (Box 482)
    - Biofuels, 2007 (Box 482)
    - Criminalization of Social Protest Latin America, 2006-2007 (Box 482)
    - Fights Based Development, Concept Papers, 2002 (Box 482)
    - ESCR Conference Mexico, 2002 (Box 482)
    - Alternatives to Neo-Liberalism Conference, 2002 (Box 482)
    - Beyond Neo-Liberalism, 1997-2000 (Box 482)
    - Profound Re-orientations, 1982 (Box 483)
    - Intelligence Oversight, 1990-1995 (Box 483)
    - Police-Military Intelligence (documents in Spanish), 1987-1995 (Box 483)
    - Miscellaneous Articles, Intel, Security, 1982-1994 (Box 483)
    - Assorted Publications, Zalaquett, J., 1987-1989 (Box 483)
    - Themes and Debates in Public Security Reform, 2000 (Box 483)
    - Miscellaneous WOLA Publications, 1997-2005 (Box 483)
    - "Demilitarizing Public Order", 1995 (Box 483)
    - International Security, Terrorism, 2005 (Box 484)
    - JIATF South, 2005 (Box 484)
    - Thailand, 2001-2004 (Box 484)
    - Southcom/DOD (old), 1991-1997 (Box 484)
    - Rapid Reaction Force, 2005 (Box 484)
    - US Southcom Human Rights Initiative, 2002 (Box 484)
    - Defense Authority and Applications, 2006 (Box 484)
    - Defense Authority, 2004 (Box 484)
- Accession (2017-0169) (Box 485-494)
  Conditions Governing Access
  Boxes 485-494 are closed until processing.